# Andrea Lea-Trengrouse

## Summary

Full-stack web developer with a background in Business Management and skills from university in full-stack web development tools such as JavaScript, React, MySQL, MongoDB, Node, and Express. I enjoy utilising my education and skills set to build a more intuitive user experience on the web. Passionate about developing, with a focus on pleasant and inbuilt user experience.

## **Technical Skills**

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, AWS Code Star, AWS

Tools: Express, React, Node, Handlebars, Query, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

### **Projects**

Social Platform API | https://github.com/Invogue01/social-platform-api

- Real-world social media app REST API with login, register, and all CRUD operations
- Start to finish coding showcased in a video using Postman
- Mongo DB models with Node.js routes and Express

Job Search and Jobs Advertisement for Coders | https://github.com/Invogue01/python-gig

- Freelance Coding gigs search Website display gig description, skills needed and, project budget
- Backend, Handlebars, debugging, homepage styling
- Mongo DB models with Node.js routes and Express, Handlebars and HTML for front end

Note Taking App. Stay organised | https://github.com/Invogue01/note-taking-app

- Helps you by reminding things and being more organised, utilises Local Storage
- Start to finish coding
- CSS3, Inquirer, HTML5, JavaScript, LocalStorage

### **Experience**

Section Administrator 2019-present

#### **Network Rail**

Attention to detail for all Data Input responsibilities. Weekly timesheets submissions alongside weekly reports and roster management. Booking company vehicles for safety checks, MOT and installations. Safety crucial tools calibration management on weekly bases combined with placing orders for PPE, Stationary and local Stores.

Payroll Administrator 2017-2019

## **Thomas & Young accountants**

Maintaining payroll information by collecting, calculating, and entering data for over 1000 employees and 350 businesses with emphasis on accuracy and attention to detail. Processing Statutory payments and RTIs. Preparing reports by compiling summaries of earnings, taxes, deductions, leave, disability, and non-taxable wages. Pension contribution submissions with NEST and Peoples Pensions. Resolving payroll discrepancies by collecting and analysing information. Providing payroll information and answering queries by phone, email or inhouse.

#### **Accounts and Payroll Administrator**

2015-2017

#### **Euroseal Ltd.**

Processing payroll and pensions on weekly bases. Bookkeeping and keeping company accounts including cash accounts reconciliation alongside banking. Processing purchase and sales ledger on daily bases. Accounts reports on weekly and monthly basis – Trial Balance, Balance Sheet, Profit and Loss. Managing credit control and issuing invoices.

## **Education**

## **Boot Camp Certificate: University Birmingham**

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in JavaScript, SQL, Big Data, React, MongoDB, Node, Express. Employing GitHub, Heroku, Docker, Postman and other tools for coding and deployment purposes.

### **RQF Level 6 diploma: University College Birmingham**

3 years programme for Business Management and Administration degree.

### **Upper secondary education. Qualifications include:**

Lithuanian Language (B)

Biology (B)

English Language (A)

Physics (C)

Mathematics (Statistics) (C)

IT (A)

History (B)

Chemistry (C)

Art and Music (A)

### **Certificate of maturity Exam:**

Mathematics- CCC (70 percent)

Biology- BCC (75 percent)

Lithuanian Language-BBC (80 percent)

History- BBC (80 percent)

English Language- ABB (90 percent)